(soft music begins)
(thunder booming)
♪ Baby are you down,
down, down, down, down ♪
♪ Even if the sky
is falling down ♪
♪ You oughta know ♪
♪ Tonight is the
night to let it go ♪
♪ Put on a show ♪
♪ I wanna see how
you lose control ♪
♪ So leave it behind 'cause
we have a night to get away ♪
♪ So come on and fly with me,
as we make our great escape ♪
♪ So baby don't worry,
you are my only ♪
♪ You won't be lonely, even
if the sky is falling down ♪
♪ You'll be my only,
no need to worry ♪
♪ Baby are you down,
down, down, down, down ♪
♪ Even if the sky
is falling down ♪
♪ Just let it be, come on and
bring your body next to me ♪
♪ I'll take you away, hey ♪
♪ Turn this place into
our private getaway ♪
♪ So leave it behind 'cause
we have a night to get away ♪
♪ So come on and fly with me,
as we make our great escape ♪
♪ So why don't we run away ♪
♪ Baby don't worry,
you are my only ♪
♪ You won't be lonely, even
if the sky is falling down ♪
♪ You'll be my only,
no need to worry ♪
♪ Baby are you down
down down down down ♪
down down down down
oooh are you down ♪
♪ Even if the sky
is falling down ♪
♪ Down like she 'posed to be ♪
♪ She gets down for me ♪
♪ Down like her temperature,
'cause to me she zero degrees ♪
♪ She cold, over freeze ♪
♪ I got that girl
from overseas ♪
♪ Now she my Miss America ♪
♪ Now can I be her
soldier please ♪
♪ I'm fighting for this girl ♪
♪ On a battlefield of love ♪
♪ Don't it look like baby cupid
sendin' arrows from above ♪
♪ Don't you ever
leave the side of me ♪
♪ Indefinitely, not probably ♪
♪ And honestly, I'm
down like the economy ♪
♪ Baby don't worry,
you are my only ♪
♪ You won't be lonely, even
if the sky is falling down ♪
♪ You'll be my only,
no need to worry ♪
♪ Baby are you down,
down, down, down, down ♪
♪ The sky is falling
Even if the
sky is falling down ♪
♪ Ooh, no ♪
♪ And the sky is falling down ♪
♪♪♪